http://www.sparklit.com/agreements.spark?agreement=privacy

Privacy Statement
SparkLIT recognizes your right to confidentiality and is committed to protecting your privacy. This privacy
statement discloses what information we gather, how we use it, and how to correct or change it. You can expect
to be notified of:
What personally identifiable information of yours is collected.
What organization is collecting the information.
How the information is used.
With whom the information may be shared.
What choices you have regarding the collection, use and distribution of the information.
What kinds of security procedures are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information
under the company’s control.
How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.
You should direct questions regarding this statement to any of our listed methods of contact: https://adbutler.com/contact-us.spark
Your personal information
We do not collect personal information when you visit our site unless you signup for a service, place an order,
register, complete a survey or enter a contest.
When you signup for a service, we will ask you for the following personal information: name and e-mail address.
We may use your personal information to contact you for account purposes.
When you place an order (upgrade to a paid version of software), we will ask you for the following personal
information: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number, and credit card number and its expiration
date. This information is requested to verify your identity. This information is transmitted via a secure
encrypted server using Transport Layer Security (TLS) encryption, more commonly known as HTTPS, the approved
industry standard (see Security section below). We may use your personal information to contact you for
account purposes.
When you submit feedback or questions via e-mail, or contact us for information about our Web site, we will
request your name and e-mail address. We use this information solely to respond to your inquiries.
We share general demographic information with advertisers and partners as aggregated information that cannot be
used in any way to identify you.
All performance statistics and data is kept private and not released to any of our partners without your
permission. Occasionally, we may reference our own statistics, but the data will be an aggregate of our
whole client base, and not identify any one party.
AdButler certifies that all personal information relating to its members and clients, including email addresses
and personal information, will be kept confidential. We do not share, sell, rent or barter any identifiable
personal information to any third party without your permission.
Company information
You agree that AdButler may identify your company name and/or logo as an AdButler customer on client lists,
marketing materials and/or press releases. If you wish to be excluded from this program, do so by emailing:
"marketing AT adbutler.com".
Security
AdButler uses Transport Layer Security (TLS) encryption, more commonly known as HTTPS, for all of the data that
we send and receive. This ensures that all user data in transit is both safe and secure, and additionally only
available to the intended recipients. This ensures that online transactions and the transmission of personal
information such as credit card details are safe from third-party interception.
Cookies
To better serve you, we use "cookies" to reduce the time required to login. A cookie is a small amount of
information sent from a Web server to your computer. We use cookies to retrieve certain information you
previously provided to AdButler, so that you do not need to reenter this information every time you login into
the members area. Additionaly we use cookies to prevent multiple votes on our Web Poll and Survey services.
Cookies are not used to access information entered on the secure server; this information can only be accessed
when you enter your name and password. No other company has access to our cookies. We do not use the cookie to
track your Internet activity once you leave AdButler.
Your choice/opt out
AdButler provides you with the opportunity to remove your personal information from our database and opt out of
receiving communications from us at any time. Login to the members section and delete any products that you have
signed for (See FAQ for more information).
If you would like to opt out of all AdButler cookies, you can do so here.
AdButler provides you with the opportunity to update or change any information you previously provided. Please
login to the members area and make your changes (See FAQ for more information).
Your consent
By using our Web site, you consent to AdButler collecting and using this information as outlined here. If we ever
change our privacy policy, we will post any changes on this page so you are always aware of the information we
collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we disclose it.
Bot/Data Collection
AdButler and its affiliates will never affix any spybot or data collection software to any of its products.
Your comments/how to reach us
If you have questions or comments about AdButler's privacy policy, please feel free to contact us.
SPARKLIT
Passionately Crafting Web Services
At Sparklit, we're focused on finding unique solutions through reliable, efficient, and innovative web apps.
Since 1998, our suite of simple-to-use tools have helped countless companies leverage the web to grow their business and increase their profitability.
“Love your company’s stuff and really appreciate the first class customer support!”
- Rick Bateman
Copyright © 2020, Sparklit All Rights Reserved. Terms of
Service • Privacy Statement • Security Statement.
